Lisa: The Highland Hotel’s 20 miles from here.
Mel: Fine. No problem.
Let’s go there.
Lisa: Yes.
Alfie’s asleep now.
Mel: Great.
Lisa: Mel! Look!
A police car!
Mel: OK, OK.
Officer: Good evening.
Turn off the engine, please.
Thank you.
Can I see your driver’s license?
Mel: What’s the problem, officer?
Officer: One of your back lights isn’t on.
Mel: Oh. I’m very sorry, officer.
We’re on our way to the Highland Hotel.
We’re very close to it now.
And we have a baby.
Officer: Ah, what a beautiful baby!
What’s his name?
Lisa: Alfie.
Officer: Oh, sorry!
OK… go to your hotel.
But please drive slowly.
And fix your light.
There’s a garage near the hotel.
Mel: Yes – thank you, officer.
Officer: Goodbye.
Goodbye, Alfie!
Mel: Good job, Alfie…